(crowd cheering and clapping)
(upbeat music)
(upbeat groovy music)
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Hey, yeah ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Aha ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I wanna dance ♪
♪ Clock strikes upon the hour ♪
♪ And the sun begins to fade ♪
♪ Still enough time to figure out ♪
♪ How to chase my blues away ♪
♪ I've done alright up to now ♪
♪ It's the light of
day that shows me how ♪
♪ And when the night falls,
the loneliness calls ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ I've been in love and lost my senses ♪
♪ Spinning through the town ♪
♪ Sooner or later, the fever ends ♪
♪ And I wind up feeling down ♪
♪ I need a man who'll take a chance ♪
♪ On a love that burns
hot enough to last ♪
♪ So when the night falls ♪
♪ My lonely heart calls ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Somebody who, somebody who ♪
♪ Somebody who loves me, yeah ♪
♪ To hold me in his arms, oh ♪
♪ I need a man who'll take a chance ♪
♪ On a love that burns
hot enough to last ♪
♪ So when the night falls ♪
♪ My lonely heart calls ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Dance ♪
♪ Come on, baby ♪
♪ Whoo, yeah ♪
♪ Dance ♪
♪ Now get with this, whoa ♪
♪ Don't you wanna dance with me, baby ♪
♪ Don't you wanna dance with me, boy ♪
♪ Hey, don't you wanna
dance with me, baby ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me
♪ ♪ Don't you wanna dance ♪
♪ Say you wanna dance ♪
♪ Don't you wanna dance ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Dance ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Dance ♪
♪ Hey, baby ♪